We have four key elements from
that release.  The first is that we
created a gentic canvas.  If you've ever
used a design tool, you're always
faced with this infinite canvas where
you can draw, where you can place
components that you bring from a library.
Ours works like this.  You can
create components directly in
React, create software components, and then
you can literally take that
component and bring it into your app.
So much so that the design of Agent 4 was
built on Replit.  All my
designers, the only tool they use is
Reprit, I didn't even have to
force them.  We brought this
experience that we call teamwork.
Your role is no longer that of a
builder, but you practically become a
project manager.  Brainstorm with
people, and once you've figured out
the plan, we'll take your task,
send it to the background, and start
processing it automatically.
We created this layer based on the
general idea that you can still run
agents in parallel, but we
made it completely opaque.  It can
be up to 10 times more productive,
literally build software 10
times faster than before, but don't you
realize what this
extra complexity is?  And the best thing is
also the fact that compared to
previous versions of people, yes, it's
very interesting that it's autonomous,
but they also become quite boring
because you're there, if it runs for an hour
, you get up, go talk to a
colleague, get a coffee, but now
you can stay in the flow.  I'm
the project manager, people do the rest
for me.  The last thing, and also
the very important one, is that we have
opened up a little bit the amount of skills that
people have.  You can build your own
software app, you can make your own slides, you can
make your own memo, and we have a long
list of skills that we support.  What
I'm trying to get across, especially to
people who don't come from a
coding background, is that at this
point you can think about your
startup idea and literally do zero to
one on repit.  What?